11/20: 
+designed program and made (rough) UML of program
11/23: 
+made the classes Controller, Loaner, Product, Book, Movie, OtherMedia, OtherLoaner, and UnitTester. 
+Made ID system, and made it work (see code for details)
+Made constructors for each class work
+Controller has list of all things to be used
11/24: 
+Made CSV Files to put data into
+Made sample data
+Made a window appear using swing graphics to do stuff in (very basic, copy-pasted from online tutorial. will use once program functions (probably))
12/3: 
*Turned due date and issuance date from int to Calendar objects
+Added testing ivolving due dates for later usage
-Removed month due, year due, and day due methods from Product and all child classes
*Made product constructors not rely on list of all products in Controller (this changes the fundamental structure of how data is stored in the program. this is why I took 2 hours to make this change)
12/4: 
+Implemented issue method. it may be buggy
+Implemented returnProduct method. may be buggy
-removed daysUntilDue method. (seems useless if I can call days between feature in Controller)
*made loaner constructor rely on Controller's CSV file, and not ArrayList in Controller
-Removed ArrayLists listOfAllProducts and listOfAllLoaners. full independence from the lists has been achieved.
12/5:
*Made max issuance different for students and teachers
+Added Window and GUI. it can toggle between loaners and products
*Fixed critical bug in Loaner and (Product?) constructor in which a loop went too far down
*Fixed bug forgetting to set ID of new teacher when selecting it
*Fixed bug forgetting to update books owned string list
*Fixed multiple bugs from copy pasting code involving a. confusing <= and <, and b. not writing String.valueOf() for longs and ints
-Removed will to live
12/6:
*Fixed and made bug-free the return button
+Implemented check due date button
*Changed a -1 to 0 in listSelectionListener so you cant select the title columns
+made buttons to display both weekly reports
+made buttona nd textfield to edit names onto
+made a limit for students and teachers for books and products issued (hard-coded (sorry))
*made files relative 

plans:
export project somehow (as .jar?)